{
    "subject": "resource/The_Angry_God",
    "predicate": "property/screenplay",
    "object": "Lester Crocker",
    "human_readable": "The screenplay of The Angry God was written by Lester Crocker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9312818646430969,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for The Angry God?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9202607274055481,
            "question": "What is the name of the screenplay written by Lester Crocker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8863133192062378,
            "question": "Is Lester Crocker known for writing screenplays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8255296349525452,
            "question": "What other films have screenplays written by Lester Crocker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5443609952926636,
            "question": "What genre might The Angry God belong to based on its screenplay writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4369242787361145,
            "question": "Was The Angry God a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3418121039867401,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of The Angry God?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3311695456504822,
            "question": "Are there any other works by Lester Crocker that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30066433548927307,
            "question": "What is the significance of The Angry God in film history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12073083221912384,
            "question": "Has Lester Crocker won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The screenplay of The Angry God was written by Lester Crocker.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3073_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of The Angry God in film history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3073_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other works by Lester Crocker that you know of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3073_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of The Angry God?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3073_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3073_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n{\n\"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3073/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt contains the sentence \"The Angry GodDirected byVan Campen HeilnerScreenplay byLester Crocker\", which confirms that Lester Crocker wrote the screenplay of The Angry God."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that the screenplay for \"The Angry God\" was written by Lester Crocker, which supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}